<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-12-24T14:23:22-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Ephram’s Book Reviews</title><subtitle>Reviews of children&apos;s book by an avid reader.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Peter Nimble</title><link href="/2025/01/12/Peter_Nimble.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Peter Nimble" /><published>2025-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2025/01/12/Peter_Nimble</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/12/Peter_Nimble.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="peter-nimble-and-his-fantastic-eyes">Peter Nimble and His Fantastic Eyes</h1>
<h3 id="author-jonathan-auxier">Author: <a href="">Jonathan Auxier</a></h3>
<h3 id="rating-1010">Rating: 10/10</h3>

<p>Peter Nimble is a child with extraorinary capabilities, he is a theif in an ordinary town, when he discovers a box of eyes, he embarks on a journey to find a missing island, and discover secrets about his past.</p>

<p>This book was very well writen, and kept the suspense well, the plot was very interesting and enjoyable, with the intriguing twist of the main protaganist being a theif. In conclusion, I really enjoyed this book and would recomend it.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Nimble and His Fantastic Eyes Author: Jonathan Auxier Rating: 10/10]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sophie Quire</title><link href="/2025/01/12/Sophie_Quire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sophie Quire" /><published>2025-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2025/01/12/Sophie_Quire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/12/Sophie_Quire.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="sophie-quire-and-the-last-storyguard">Sophie Quire and the Last Storyguard</h1>
<h3 id="author-jonathan-auxier">Author: <a href="">Jonathan Auxier</a></h3>
<h3 id="rating-1010">Rating: 10/10</h3>

<p>The Sequel to <a href="https://ephramstevens.github.io/book_reviews//2025/01/12/Peter_Nimble.html">Peter Nimble and His Fantastic Eyes</a> Sophie Quire and the Last Storyguard takes place in a town where books are hated and burned. One day, Peter Nimble brings her a special book, which unlocks a whole new world of magic. I really liked this book because books were a centeral part of the plot. This book brings back Peter Nimble and Sir Tode, and introduces Sophie and a new villain, who like King Incarnadine, seeks to destroy magic and make things in his city “normal”.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Quire and the Last Storyguard Author: Jonathan Auxier Rating: 10/10]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ranger’s Aprentice - The Ruins of Gorlan</title><link href="/2025/01/12/Ranger's_Aprentice.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ranger’s Aprentice - The Ruins of Gorlan" /><published>2025-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2025/01/12/Ranger&apos;s_Aprentice</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/12/Ranger&apos;s_Aprentice.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="rangers-aprentice---the-ruins-of-gorlan">Ranger’s Aprentice - The Ruins of Gorlan</h1>
<h3 id="author-john-flanagan">Author: <a href="">John Flanagan</a></h3>
<h3 id="rating-1010">Rating: 10/10</h3>

<p>Ranger’s Aprentice is a series about a boy named Will, who grows up in the ward of Castle Redmond. On Chosing Day, when the children of the ward are chosen as aprentices, Will becomes aprenticed to the mysterious Ranger Halt. Will begins to learn what it means to be a Ranger, and undertakes a dangerous mission, which could have disasterous consequences.</p>

<p>This book grabed me from the start, Will is a very likeable protaganist and the story is very interesting, leaving space for many more adventures. Another thing that I enjoyed about this series is that there is no overarching plot, only single adventures.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ranger’s Aprentice - The Ruins of Gorlan Author: John Flanagan Rating: 10/10]]></summary></entry></feed>